ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
ShinY
深影
■
ShinY
深影
■
翻译： 明月 弓潭 天才王旺旺 黑猫 cynthia
奉圣父 圣子
In the name of the Father, the Son,
■
校对： Michelle 碳树    压制：AlliumFistulosum
圣灵之名
and the Holy Spirit.
神父 请饶恕我的罪
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
我们得聊聊
We need to talk.
ShinY
深影
■
你有尊重的圣礼吗 勒孔特先生
Are there any sacraments you do respect, Mr. LeConte?
我尊重所有圣礼
All of them.
所以我履行我本份
That's why I do what I do.
你尽你职守
That's why you do what you do.
ShinY
深影
所以神圣的男男女女可以置身事外
So holy men and women can keep their hands clean.
ShinY
深影
我不会替你动克里斯汀和她女儿的
I won't help you with Kristen and her daughter.
这事和她们没关系
That's not what this is about.
这事是什么事
What "what" is about?
在接下来的几天 主教会给你
The Monsignor will be approaching you
布置一个紧急任务
in the next few days with an emergency assessment.
你听指挥行动
You will do what is asked.
要做什么
Which is?
我不知道
I don't know.
在任务里
But someone during the assessment
接头人会说"乡村酒吧"这个词
will say the word "honky-tonk."
你听到这个词后
When you hear this word, you will count
往后数十二个词
to the 12th word spoken after it,
把那个词告诉我
and that is the word you will bring back to me.
你疯了吗
Are you nuts?
我很认真的
I couldn't be more deathly serious.
再说一遍 他说完"乡村酒吧"这个词
Once again, you will hear the word "honky-tonk,"
再往后数的第十二个词
then you will count to the 12th word spoken after that.
就是我要的答案
That is the word I need to hear.
- 我为什么要做这个 - 这是机密
- And why am I doing this? - That is confidential.
我只能告诉你 这和克里斯汀没关系
All I can tell you is, it has nothing to do with Kristen.
你听到第十二个词之后
When you have the 12th word,
打这个电话
you will call this number.
我会把它留在座位上
I'm leaving it here on the seat.
你打通之后说
You will call the number and say,
"我的柴犬腿瘸了
"My Shiba Inu is limping,
我要找米迦勒医生"
and I need to speak to Dr. Michael."
这对你来说就是个游戏吧
This is all a game to you, isn't it?
一个很严肃的游戏
A very serious game,
我们需要玩它来保卫神圣
and one we have to play to protect the holy.
阿门
Amen.
谢谢你 神父
Thank you, Father.
你好
Hi there.
好久不见
Long time no see.
不 这不可能...
No, this is not...
再发生了
happening again.
你已经走了
You were gone.
起床了 瞌睡虫
Wake up, sleepyhead.
看看我带来了谁
Look who I have with me.
嗨 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
不要
No.
醒醒
Wake up.
醒过来
你今天是好孩子还是坏孩子
Were you a good girl today or a bad one?
- 我是好孩子 - 嘿
- I was good. - Yay.
看看我的新视频
Look at my new video.
我收到了很多点赞
I'm getting a lot of up votes.
闭上你的
Close your...
眼睛
eyes.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
紧紧地
Tighter.
我去
Holy fuck.
常用联系人 正在致电 大卫
- 克里斯汀 - 大卫 我需要
- Kristen? - David, I need
跟你聊聊 就现在
to talk to you right now.
马上来
On my way.
进来
Come in.
我们聊聊
We need to talk.
好
Good.
我想知道几个问题
I need some questions answered.
维克多·勒孔特跟我说
Victor LeConte told me
利兰·汤森从一开始就
that I was being pursued by Leland Townsend,
追踪我
from the very beginning,
企图通过我
that he had designs on one of my daughters,
培养
and that he was grooming her
我的其中一个女儿
through me.
这是真的吗
Is this correct?
- 那是他的说辞 - 你不相信他
- That's what he said. - You don't believe him?
我觉得一个间谍看什么都像是阴谋
I believe a spy sees everything as a conspiracy.
好 我们晚点再说这个
Okay, we'll get back to that.
过去两年内发生的所有
Everything that's happened in the last two years,
从利兰接近我
from the moment that Leland approached me
到现在
to now,
都是设计好的
has been by design?
维克多是那么想的
That's what Victor thinks.
你是怎么设计的
What about your designs?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你对我的示好
Your pursuit of me,
从一开始让我做这个工作
from the moment you invited me to do this job
到我们现在的关系
to our relationship now,
所有都是设计好的吗
has everything been by design?
什么
What?
不是
No.
如果利兰从一开始就追踪我
If Leland was pursuing me from the beginning,
你是说 你刚好在那时候
are you saying that it's just coincidental
给我介绍工作 完全是巧合吗
that you invited me to do this job at that exact time?
我不知道利兰是怎么想的
Look, I can't speak to what Leland thinks.
我确定的是 我是因为你的才能
I can only say that I invited you to be an assessor
才邀请你做顾问 而不是什么圈套
based on your talent, not because of some design.
我为什么要相信你
And why should I trust you?
因为我说的是事实
Because I tell you the truth.
不 你不是 你没有过
No, you don't. No, you haven't.
你给那个组织工作了多久了
How long have you been working for the Entity?
过去几周的神秘电话
All those mysterious phone calls in the last couple weeks,
都是这个勒孔特打的
they've all been from this LeConte guy?
每次你都撒谎了
And every time, you lied about it?
你一句话都说不出来
You can't even talk to me now
因为你一张嘴就会是谎话
because everything you say will be a lie.
我答应给维克多·勒孔特干活
I agreed to work with Victor LeConte.
他是在做好事
He was doing good work,
而且我觉得这是在帮助神
and I thought it was a way to help God.
是他让你骗我的
And he asked you to lie to me.
我不能把这个工作告诉任何人
I couldn't tell anyone about the work I did with them.
我甚至不能告诉主教
I couldn't even tell the Monsignor.
大卫 我不相信
David, I don't believe
神和教堂 但我喜欢你做的事
in God and the Church, but I always liked that you did
因为那些事让我渴望
because it gave me something to aspire to,
让我敬佩
something to admire.
结果你和其他人也没什么不同
But you're just like everyone else.
你说得对
You're right.
原谅我
Forgive me.
- 所以 现在呢 - 现在
- So, now what? - Now
我告诉你所有我知道的RSM生育诊所的事
I tell you everything I know about their pursuit of RSM.
还有莱克萨斯
And Lexis?
对
Yes.
- 等等 你要干嘛 - 我得先确认一下
- Wait, wh... what are you doing? - I have to go check something.
那我们的工作呢
And our work?
我需要赚钱
I need the money,
但我觉得这事太离谱了
but I feel pretty fucked over,
得花一阵时间消化
and it's gonna take me a while to adjust to that.
有我失踪卵子的消息吗 已发送
有点眉目 有酒吗
你还好吗
You okay?
- 谢谢 - 没事
- Thank you. - No problem.
- 你给我准备什么了 - 好吧
- What have you got? - Okay.
不
No,
我要成年人的饮料 我是成年人了
I want an adult drink. I'm an adult.
我要像成年人一样喝酒
I want to drink like one.
好吧
Okay.
- 我的天 - 怎么了
- Oh, my God. - What?
你家成年人喝的东西跟小孩一样吗
Even your adult drinks look like kids' drinks.
- 我知道了 我来拿 - 不 我来
- I got it, I got it. - Oh, no, I got it.
所以
So...
- 你想要个进展报告吗 - 是的
- you want a progress report? - I do.
抱歉我太焦虑了
I'm sorry to be so anxious.
这个是去年的
Okay, this one is last year.
我们生育记录的第一轮议案
Our first motion for production of records.
- 嗯 - 这个是六个月之前的
- Right. - This one was six months ago.
我们生育记录的第一份诉讼
Our first lawsuit for production of same.
- 好的 - 这是他们第一次被拒绝
- Yeah. - This is their first rejection.
嗯 好 我都想起来了
Okay, yeah, it's all coming back to me.
这个是两个月前
This one is two months ago.
威胁我们赔四千三百万美元的诉讼
Our threatened lawsuit of $43 million.
没错
Right.
这是RSM生育诊所一周后的示警回应
This is RSM's alarmed response one week later.
这个 亲爱的
And this... Whew, girl.
这是法官对RSM生育诊所的判决书
This is the judge’s summary judgment against RSM
他们必须拿出你丢失的卵子
to produce your missing egg
否则将会被追究责任
or be held liable.
还有… 你闻
And this... smell this.
还能闻到他们的汗味
You can almost smell their sweat.
这是一个成年人面对四千三百万美元的官司
That's what threatening a $43 million suit
所要付出的代价
does to grown men.
谢谢你 贾思敏
Thank you, Yasmine.
最有意思的是
That's always the most fun part.
他们承认还有第十二颗卵子
They admitted there was a 12th egg
档案系统出错了
and that their filing system made the error.
所以 我还有一颗卵子在外面
So, I do have another egg out there?
他们已经有线索了
And they have a lead on it.
线索 什么意思
Okay, a lead. Wh... What does that mean exactly?
你可能还想喝一口
You may want another sip.
- 什么意思 - 我对他们的记录提出了起诉
- Uh-oh. - I sued for their records,
他们说你丢失的那颗卵子
and they indicate that your missing egg
被误捐给了医学研究机构
was mistakenly donated to medical research.
- 所以它已经被破坏了 - 应该是
- Okay, so it's been destroyed? - Probably.
你的卵子有可能被捐给了一对夫妇
There is a chance your egg was donated to a couple.
等等 你说什么
Wait, what?
被捐给… 捐给谁
Donated... donated where?
这家医学研究机构过去曾向
This medical research facility has donated eggs
有需要的夫妇捐赠卵子
to recipient couples in the past.
如果你需要的话我会继续跟进这件事
I'll stay on it if you want.
- 那太好了 - 好
- Yeah, that would be great. - Okay.
克里斯汀还在团队里吗
Is Kristen on the team anymore?
- 在 - 呃...
- Yes. - Uh...
我给她打过电话了 她说马上就到
I called her. She said she's coming.
先不等她了 我们开始吧
Okay, well, let's start.
现在有个紧急任务
This is an emergency assessment.
教区里有人开了家玩具店
A friend of the parish has a toy store,
这个就是店里的玩具
and this came from it.
这是什么 恐怖玩具吗
Okay. What are we looking at, haunted toys?
你按一下魔杖
Use the wand.
地狱见
See you in hell.
好吧
Okay.
确实很恐怖 但…
That's creepy, but, uh,
也许只是制造过程中的恶作剧
probably just a prank in the manufacturing.
不止这个
It's not just that toy.
很多玩具都出了问题
A lot of the toys are causing problems.
克里斯汀
Kristen.
主教 本
Monsignor, Ben.
大卫
David.
- 我们要打扮成这样吗 - 是啊 公主殿下
- We getting costumes with that? - Yeah, you're the princess.
- 一家恐怖玩具店 - 认真的吗
- A haunted toy store. - Seriously?
- 地狱见 - 店主
- See you in hell. - The store manager
向我们反映
has complained that his patrons
顾客一直在退货
have been returning some of the items,
有些顾客投诉说
and some have complained of demonic infestation
这些玩具被恶魔附体
coming from the toys.
- 听起来又劳碌又无关紧要 - 也许吧
- Sounds like busywork. - Possibly,
但你们还是去查查
but just look into it.
你今天怎么这么安静 大卫
You're quiet today, David.
失眠了
Uh, long night.
绿点玩具
这些都是上周
These are the returns
被退回来的玩具
just from last week.
- 大家都很害怕它们 - 为什么
- Everybody's terrified of them. - Why?
觉得它们很恐怖
Just something creepy about them.
我给牧师看了小公主魔棒
I showed the parish the Little Princess Magic Wand.
这里还有四根一样的
Here's four more, same thing.
还有这些毛绒玩具
And the stuffed animals, too. Look at them.
- 所以大家为什么要买呢 - 他们买的时候
- So, why did people buy ‘em? - They weren't like that
这些玩具可不是这样 它们本来是这样的
when they bought them. They were like this.
这些看上去都像是仿制品
These all look like knockoffs.
会不会是
You think there's a chance
制造环节出了问题
there was a problem in the manufacturing?
有可能 但问题是什么
I guess, but what is the problem?
为什么会出问题
And why?
为什么大家会这么害怕
Why are people so creeped out?
救救我 我被困在地狱里了
本
Ben.
别紧张 只是起恶作剧罢了
Okay, come on. This is a prank.
真的吗 "救救我 我被困在地狱里了"
Really? "Help me, I'm in hell"?
我们也想过这种可能
We looked into that as a possibility,
但这些玩具唯一的共同点
but the only thing that these toys
就是被退回的时间一致
have in common is timing.
退货大约发生在两周前
The returns started about two weeks ago,
但这些东西我们已经卖了很多年
even though we've sold these products for years
- 此前没有任何问题 - 所以两周前
- and had no issues. - So something occurred
发生了一些事情 影响了店里的存货
two weeks ago that affected the existing stock?
听上去像是群体性臆病
Sounds like contagious hysteria.
一个人说有问题 所有人都会这么说
One person says something’s wrong, and then everybody does.
又或者恶魔真的存在
Or a demonic presence.
我能把这些带回家做分析吗
Can I take these home and analyze them?
当然
Yes, please.
什么声音
What's that?
那个…
Oh, yeah, that.
隔壁是家乡村音乐酒吧
It's a honky-tonk next door.
他们总是很早就开始排练
They're always rehearsing early.
我们投诉过 但从未起效
We complain, but it never matters.
从未起效
Never matters?
是的
Never.
什么事
What was it?
第十二个词 是"起效"
12th word. "Matters."
"它们起效"还是"它起效"
"Matter" or "matters"?
"它起效" 怎么了
"Matters." Why?
七个字母
Seven letters.
一 二 三
One, two, three,
四
four,
五
five,
六 七
six, seven.
是格蕾丝的事吗 格蕾丝·林
Is it about Grace? Grace Ling?
无可奉告
I can't tell you that.
谢谢你 大卫
Thank you, David.
你今天帮了教会和上帝
You have offered a great service
一个大忙
to the Church and God today.
你现在能把格蕾丝弄出来吗
Can you get Grace out now?
我不能说 但…
I can't tell you, but...
她还活着
she is alive.
小丑玩具盒 当盖子被揭开 一个小丑就会突然跳出来
救救我 我被困在地狱里了
《邪恶》第三季第八集
动起来
Move.
会好的
It's okay.
《为人父母之魔》
嘿 克里斯汀
Hey, Kristen.
嗨 贾思敏 我很抱歉
Hi, Yasmine. I'm... I'm so sorry.
我做了个噩梦 我
I just had a nightmare, and I...
我想知道...
I just need to know...
我知道
Yes.
怎么了
Yes, what?
几个小时前我刚刚查到
I just found out a few hours ago.
你的卵子不是被捐给医学研究机构
Your egg wasn't donated to medical research.
而是被捐给另一家生育诊所
It was donated to another fertility clinic.
我本来打算早上告诉你
I was gonna call you in the morning.
它现在在哪
Where is it?
它已经受精了
It's been fertilized,
被植入另一个女性体内
and it's been implanted into another woman.
孩子们 是时候开始动笔了
Now, children, it's time to write.
该死
Damn it.
涅琵日需要保持静默 它与上帝连结
为什么这么难
Why is it so hard?
所以...
So...
你打算抓我吗
you're trying to catch me?
试试呗
Just try.
这些头发是怎么回事
So, tell me about this hair.
修女安德莉亚的头发 你梦寐以求的东西
It's Sister Andrea's. It's what you wanted.
这也太少了
It's kind of light.
我希望她不要秃顶
I hope the good sister's not going bald.
你的承诺呢 缪斯女神并没有来
Where's your end of the deal? The muse isn't coming.
这几根头发的量
This amount would maybe
最多能给你换几个逗号的灵感 不会再多了
buy you a few commas, not much more.
你从她梳子上顺下来的吧
You got it out of her comb, didn't you?
是排水孔
Her drain.
你也没说我不能这么干
And you didn't say I couldn't.
我的想法是
Here's my idea.
关于你新书的主题
The subject matter of your book,
这是个相当成熟的领域 对吗
it's fairly well-trodden ground, isn't it?
- 我写的不是这个 - 你在现实中见过
- Not the way I'm writing it. - Have you ever
被恶魔附体的人吗
seen a real-life possession?
- 我参加过驱魔仪式 - 不 我说的不是
- I've been to an exorcism. - No, I'm not talking
被懦弱的神职人员绑在床上的人
about somebody tied to their bed by the cowardly clergy.
我说的是一个自由的
I'm talking about someone free,
不受束缚的
unfettered,
完全被恶魔吞噬的人
and completely consumed by the demonic.
怎么样 有趣吗
Would that be interesting?
非常
Very.
很好
Good.
到这里来 明晚
There. It's tomorrow night.
利兰·汤森 德雷登大街421号东9D室 请您务必到场
- 打个红色领带 - 准备好了吗
- Wear a red tie. - You ready?
没有
Nope.
我们不一定要这么做
We don't need to do this.
- 我知道 - 好吧
- I know. - Okay.
慢慢来 不着急
Take your time, take your time.
我在里面等你 好吗
I'll meet you inside, okay?
好的
All right.
你怀孕多久了
How far along are you?
作为温迪格夫妻的律师
As the Wendigs' lawyer,
我想说明一下 我们同意这次会面
I want to make clear, we agreed to this meeting
是出于善意的
as a goodwill gesture.
问这个问题并非出于恶意 怀亚特
It's an innocent question, Wyatt.
我只是想说清楚 我当事人的回答
I just want to be clear. My client's answering your question
并不能够成协议
does not constitute an agreement.
我天 你就少说两句吧
Oh, my God, give it a break.
下周就八个月了
It will be eight months next week.
- 我很抱歉发生了这件事 - 别这么说
- I'm really sorry this happened. - Don't say that.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry, too.
我不太清楚事情怎么会变成这样
I'm not quite sure how we ended up here.
我
I...
我以为我的卵子已经被销毁了 所以
I thought my egg had been destroyed, so...
诊所告诉我们是来自于一位匿名捐赠者
The clinic told us it came from an anonymous donor.
没错
Right.
很奇怪 这些
It's weird. These...
改变人生的事件似乎都来自意外
life-changing events just seem to come from... accidents.
虽然这可能是你的卵子 女士
While it may be your egg, ma'am,
但我的当事人已经让它受精了
my client fertilized it,
这里面一半是他的遗传物质
making it 50% his genetic material.
但其中一半的我当事人的遗传物质
But my client's genetic material was acquired
- 是通过非法手段获取的 - 求你了
- by an illegal act... - Look, please.
克里斯汀
Kristen...
我没有生育能力
I couldn't have a baby.
我以为这辈子都没机会有孩子了
I thought it was over for me.
但后来我们接到了诊所的电话
But then we got a call from the clinic.
你得理解 这对我们来说是个奇迹
You have to understand, this is a miracle for us.
我要有宝宝了
I'm having a baby.
一个小女孩
A little girl.
萨拉
Sara.
我已经为她买好衣服了
And I have clothes for her.
还为她准备了房间
I have a room.
我爱她 我会爱她的
And I love her. I will love her.
我明白 只是
I... I understand. It's...
我不是想 破坏你的快乐
I'm not trying to... undercut your joy.
我想要你也成为她生命中的部分
I want you to be a part of her life.
我们不同意共同监护权
We will not agree to joint custody.
请你别说了
Please shut up.
与监护权无关
This isn't about that.
这和两个妈妈有关
This is about two moms.
我很乐意
I'd like that.
萨拉是个好名字
Sara's a great name.
是我祖母的名字
It was my grandmother's.
克里斯汀 我们能聊聊吗
Kristen, can we talk?
当然
Sure.
我知道这很奇怪
I... I know this is all really weird.
整件事都很奇怪
The entire situation.
但有没有什么我们应该知道的事
But is there anything we should know?
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们刚听说了有关生育所的传言
We just heard rumors about the fertility clinic.
说那边的事情有点 不对劲
That there was something... wrong there.
是真的吗
Is that true?
温迪格先生 我觉得你应该和你的律师谈谈
Mr. Wendig, I... I... I think you should talk to your lawyer.
我会的 但如果有什么
Yeah, I will, but if there's anything
你能提醒我们的 会很有帮助
you could warn us about, that would be... helpful.
发生什么事了吗
Did anything happen?
瓦莱丽 怀孕的过程
Valerie's just had such a...
相当艰难
a hard pregnancy, and...
然后
then...
当我听到宝宝的心跳时
when I listened to the baby's heartbeat,
我听到了
I... I heard, um...
你在担心宝宝的心脏吗
You're worried about the baby's heart?
不 那听起来
No, it sounded...
像别的东西
like something else.
像什么
Like what?
像
A...
咆哮
growl.
听着 我知道这么说很疯狂 但听上去真的
Look, I... I know that sounds crazy, but it... it sounded just...
和一般心跳不同 像
not normal. Like...
一个动物
an animal.
温迪格先生
Mr. Wendig,
焦虑对于待产父母来说
anxiety is normal
是正常的
for an expectant parent.
我也有过
I had it as well.
也许你是对的
Yeah, you're probably right. That...
- 这就说得通了 - 对
- that makes a lot of sense. - Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 这是什么 - 是一截断指
- What is it? - It's a severed finger.
它在巫师球里
It was inside the Wizard Ball.
- 什么 - 是的 有一截
- What? - Yeah, there was a
断指
severed finger
在巫师球里面
inside the Wizard Ball.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我正尝试着
I'm, uh, trying to
查一查生产商
trace it back to the manufacturer
因为我猜测
because I am guessing that
在生产的过程中 可能有人
there was someone there who had their finger chopped off
砍掉了手指
in the manufacturing.
你查到了什么
Anyway, what have you found?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你之前说想谈谈的
You wanted to talk.
之后再说吧
Yeah, maybe later.
现在面前的可是巫师球里的断指啊
It's not quite up to a finger in a Wizard Ball.
克里斯汀 我就是想找点事分散注意力
Kristen, I'm looking for a distraction from this craziness.
告诉我
Tell me.
遗传方面的
Genetics.
你觉得RSM生育诊所
Do you think RSM Fertility
有可能删除共情基因吗
could've deleted the empathy gene?
理论上来说 一些人格特质
Well, theoretically, certain personality traits
可以从基因上改变
can be genetically modified,
但仅仅是理论层面的
but only theoretically.
这是因为莱克萨斯吗 因为
Is this about Lexis? Because, hey,
她是个好孩子 你是位好母亲
she's a good kid, you're a good mother.
你只要保持你现在所做的就好
You just keep doing what you're doing.
不是
No, no, no. Um...
我们找到了我的
We've located my, uh,
那颗遗失的卵子 然后
my missing egg, and, um...
它已被放入一个女人的子宫
...it's been implanted,
孩子的父亲认为
and the father thinks
事情有些不对劲
something may be wrong.
- 比如什么不对劲呢 - 我不知道
- Like-like what? - I don't know.
没什么 我是说 他可能
Nothing. I... I mean, he's just, um...
我挺喜欢孩子母亲的 她
I like the mother. She... she, uh...
我只是不想有什么坏事发生
I just don't want anything bad to happen.
嘿 大卫
Hey, David.
他在呢
Yup, he's here.
好的 我们来了 再见
Okay-doke, yup, we'll come. Okay. Bye.
- 另个案子吗 - 不 是同一个
- Another case? - No, same one.
- 又一个被附体的玩具 - 嘿 嘿
- Another possessed toy. - Hey, hey, hey, hey.
我给了你想要的答案吗
Did I give you what you wanted?
我不知道 只是
I don't know. It's just that the...
那个父亲担心基因问题
the father's worried about genetics,
而我不知道和他怎么说
and I just don't know what to tell him.
先天不及后天
Nature vs. nurture.
你就这么说
That's what you say.
我坚信后天的养育更重要
I would bet on nurture every time.
你是作为朋友的身份说这话
Is that a friend speaking,
还是以科学家的身份说这话
or a scientist?
两者都是
Both.
谢谢你们能来
Thank you for coming.
店铺经理告诉我你们正在调查这些
The store manager told me you were looking into these...
奇案
strange cases.
可以告诉我们发生了什么吗
Can you tell us what happened?
这个
Uh, this.
它拼写出"撒旦一号"
It spells out "Satan-One."
看来今天没有
Not today.
它昨晚拼写了好几次
It did several times last night.
真的把我的老婆和孩子吓到了
Really freaked out the kids and my wife.
他们睡在客厅
They slept in the living room.
- 亲爱的 怎么了 - 疼死了
- Honey, honey, w... w... what's wrong? - It burns!
好疼
It burns!
什么 什么疼
What... what burns?
我的头
My head.
之前发生过这种事吗
Has this happened before?
她昨晚抱怨过自己头痛
She complained of her head hurting last night.
我们去了一家西部乡村酒吧
We went out to a country western bar,
播的都是嘈杂的乡巴佬音乐
a lot of really loud honky-tonk music.
- 乡巴佬 - 你叫医生了吗
- Honky-tonk? - Did you call a doctor?
我以为她是头痛犯了
I thought she was having a headache.
就告诉她别当回事
Told her to ignore it.
我真不应该这么做
I shouldn't have done that.
我觉得你需要找医生
I think you need to call a doctor.
爪子友好兽医服务
爪子友好宠物医院
Paws & Claws Friendly Vet Services.
请在哔声后留言
Please leave a message after the beep.
我的柴犬
My Shiba Inu
瘸了
is limping,
我需要米迦勒医生给我回电
and I need Dr. Michael to call back.
恶魔桑塔纳
Ave Santana.
我请求你附身于我
I call on thee to enter me.
I call on thee to enter.
恶魔桑塔纳
Ave Santana.
他是谁
Who is he?
我的一个病人 赛斯
One of my patients, Seth.
那些人都是谁
Who are all these people?
着魔崇拜者 他们是来这里看戏的
Possession chasers. They're here for a show.
他现在就在这 在我身上
He's here now. He's in me.
我能感觉到他 我能感觉到他的力量
I can feel him. I can feel his power.
你听说过再生疗法是一种
You've heard of rebirthing therapy as a treatment for
- 治疗反应性依恋障碍的方法吗 - 当然
- reactive attachment disorder? - Sure.
除了恶魔疗法 我还加入了这种疗法
Well, I do the same thing, except with demonic therapy.
试验者们邀请恶魔附身
The subject invites the demonic in,
然后再驱赶它
and then expels it.
这通常是治疗重度患者唯一的方法
It's often the only way to reach the grossly reactive.
- 天呐 - 恶魔桑塔纳
- Jesus. - Ave Santana.
恶魔桑塔纳 恶魔桑塔纳
Ave Santana. Ave Santana.
我与你们同在
I am with you.
这也太离奇了
This is something else. extraordinary.
不 我告诉你 亲自感受才是真离奇
No, I'll tell you what's extraordinary: experiencing it.
亲自参与其中 而不是在旁观察 参与
Being on the inside. Not observing, being.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
托马斯·沃尔夫 亨特·斯·汤普森都这么做
Tom Wolfe, Hunter S. Thompson,
均为著名美国作家 记者
他们以擅写奇闻异事出名
gonzo journalism.
这才是你的书所需要的 你被附身
This is what your book needs. You becoming possessed,
然后驱魔 再然后就可以把它写进书里
then having the demon expelled, then you write about it.
- 恶魔桑塔纳  - 那我该怎么做
- Ave Santana. - How do I do that?
恶魔桑塔纳
Ave Santana.
你打的电话
You called?
我们正在评估的那个案件
The assessment we're on,
我给过你单词回答的那个
the one with the word I gave you?
- "起效"吗 - 对
- "Matters"? - Yes.
我们被一个叫李章的男人邀请去他家
We were called to the house of a man named Li Zhang.
- 这个名字耳熟吗 - 不熟
- Is that name familiar? - No.
他的妻子夏洛特 据说被玩具附身了
His wife, Charlotte, was supposedly possessed by a toy,
但我能看出来那是表演
but I could tell it was an act.
- 好吧 - 当我们在观察她
- Okay. - While we were observing her,
评估案件时 她丈夫说出了那个单词
assessing her, her husband said the word
"乡巴佬音乐"
"honky-tonk."
这个词突然就蹦了出来
It came out of nowhere.
我数了这之后的第十二个单词
I counted 12 words after it,
那个单词是"忽视"
and the word was "ignore."
他说 "我们听了
He said, "We were listening to a lot
很多嘈杂的乡巴佬音乐
of really loud honky-tonk music.
我以为她是头痛犯了
I thought she was having a headache.
就告诉她别当回事"
Told her to ignore it."
我不知道你在等什么信息
I have no idea what message you're waiting for,
但我觉得传递过程出现了一些差错
but I think there was a mistake in the transmission,
这才是真正的信息
and this is the real message.
"忽视"
"Ignore."
或者是"忽视"你之前所收到的信息
Either "ignore" what you received before,
或者是数六个字母
or count six letters,
不是七个
not seven.
信息已经送达 你的任务完成了
The message was delivered. Your service here is complete.
先生 等等
Sir, wait.
没人会突然说"乡巴佬音乐"这个词的
Nobody just says "honky-tonk."
也许这才是信息
Maybe this is the message.
大卫
David,
你已证明自己是一个合格的中间人
you have proven yourself to be an effective intermediary,
但记住了 你的工作也仅限于此
but remember, that is all you are.
你服务他人
You serve others,
他们感到满意
and they are satisfied.
就是这里了
And here we are.
给 宝宝的连体衣
Here. Some more onesies.
准备多少都不够多
You can really never have too many.
- 谢谢你 - 他们会拉得到处都是
- Aw. Thank you. - They will poop all over them.
谢谢你 克里斯汀
Thank you, Kristen.
你知道吗 能跟经历过这事的人聊一聊
You know, it's really nice to talk to someone
感觉真的很好
who's been through this before.
我没有姐妹
I don't have any sisters.
- 你感觉如何 - 我很好
- How are you feeling? - I'm fine.
但我最近会做一些奇怪的梦
Yeah. Though I've been having these wild dreams.
- 真的吗 - 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
大火吞噬掉了一切 我怎么也逃不出来
Everything is engulfed in flames, and I can't get out.
我能听见我的孩子在哭 但却碰不到她
I can hear my baby crying, but I can't reach her.
我应该担心吗
Should I be worried?
不用 有一次怀孕时
No, I had the exact same thing.
我也经历过相同的事
With one of my pregnancies.
是黄体酮太高的原因
It's a heightened level of progesterone.
荷尔蒙 没错 有道理
Hormones. Yep, that makes sense.
事实上 我真正担心的人是罗根
Actually, who I'm worried about is Logan.
他这段时间挺不容易的
He's having a hard time.
你把所有的植物都拔了吗
Are you tearing out all your plants?
你知道鹿食草基本上都是有毒的吗
Did you know hellebore are basically lethal?
杜鹃花和百合花也是
So are azalea and lilies.
我们在外面种了一整个死亡陷阱花园
I mean, we were growing a whole death trap garden out here.
我确信你不会让你的孩子出来
Well, I'm sure you wouldn't allow your baby out
吃植物吧 但 没错
to graze on the plants, but yeah, that's...
安全点总不会有错
It's always good to be safe.
没错 至少我还能做到这些
Yeah, it's the least I can do.
对了 如果你愿意 我可以介绍一个人给你
By the way, um, I can refer you to someone if you'd like,
他能帮你解决我们谈过的焦虑问题
uh, about that thing that we spoke about, the anxiety?
哦 不用 没关系
Oh, uh, nah, that's all right.
我只是 我能看出来
I just, I... I see how much
瓦莱丽承受了多少痛苦
Valerie is suffering and...
- 我能做的却只有这么一点点 - 我理解
- how little I can do, you know? - Yeah.
你还听见过咆哮声吗
Did you hear any more of the growling
- 瓦莱丽肚子的 - 没有了
- from... from Valerie? - No.
已经过去了
Uh, that's gone.
- 那就好 - 是啊
- Well, that's great. - Yeah.
所以 这就是你工作的地方吗
So, this is where you work?
对 我猜你可能想见见我的老板
Yeah, I thought you might want to meet my boss.
但林恩 劳拉和莱拉呢
But not Lynn, Laura and Lila?
坐吧
Well, um... Here.
听着 你很特别 莱克萨斯
See, uh, you're special, Lexis.
而且我最好一次只带一个孙女来上班
And I thought I'd take one granddaughter at a time to work.
你经常给你的老板带饼干吗
Do you always bring your boss cookies?
饼干 是啊 他很喜欢饼干
Biscuits. Yeah, yeah, he loves them.
听着
Listen, um...
我想提醒你
... I want to warn you.
他也许跟你想象中的不一样
He might not look like you expect.
- 你什么意思 - 我是说
- What do you mean? - I mean...
一些人觉得他看起来很刻薄
some people think he looks a little mean
有时候他 闻起来有些奇怪
and sometimes he, like, smells a little weird.
但你只需要表现出友好和微笑就行了 好吗
But you just have to be friendly and smile, okay?
然后我晚点再跟你解释
And then we can talk about it later.
- 现在你吓到我了 - 不 不 不
- Now you're scaring me. - No, no, no, no.
我只是想你准备好
I just want you to be ready.
好吧 我有五分钟
All right, I got five minutes.
开始吧
Let's go.
先生 我带来了我的孙女莱克萨斯
Sir, I brought my granddaughter Lexis
我们还有礼物给你
and, uh, we have a present for you.
是我想的那个礼物吗
Is it what I think it is?
没错 我们给你带了饼干
Yes. We brought you biscuits.
你好
Hello.
- 莱克萨斯是吗 - 是的 先生
- Lexis, was it? - Yes, sir.
请自便
Please. Help yourself.
谢乐尔告诉了我你的不少事
I hear so much about you from Sheryl.
她认为你前途无量
She thinks you have a great future in store for you.
所以 你几年级了
So, what grade are you in?
五年级
Fifth grade.
也许有朝一日你可以来这里上班
Well, maybe someday you can work here.
我们需要聪明的年轻人
We need bright young people.
听起来不错吧
Does that sound good?
听起来不错 但我更想成为一名医生
It does, but I really want to be a doctor.
我们的遗传学部门也需要很多的医生
Well, we need more doctors in our genetics division.
好了 我该工作了
Well, I should get back to work.
谢谢你们的饼干
Thank you for the biscuits.
不用谢
You're welcome.
莱克萨斯
Lexis.
经理有多少只眼睛
How many eyes does the Manager have?
- 多少只眼睛 - 对
- How many eyes? - Yeah.
两个啊 怎么了
Two. Why?
呼 现在该干嘛
Oof. Now what?
你该复述祈祷文了
Now you recite the prayer.
"撒旦 力量之力
"Satan, force of power,
启蒙之力"
"force of enlightenment."
继续 我一会儿就回来
Keep going. I'll get that.
"撒旦 力量之力..."
"Satan, force of power..."
利兰 我得和你聊...
Leland, I have to t...
- 博格斯 - 哦
- Boggs. - Oh, shit.
好吧 我觉得你看错莱克萨斯了
Okay, I think you're wrong about Lexis.
- 你试过她了 - 对 她看不到他
- You tested her? - Yeah, she didn't see him.
- 看不到他的原形 - 我没错
- Not as he was. - I'm not wrong.
她只是需要更多正确的影响
She just needs more of the right influence.
还没结束呢
It's not over yet.
我读完了 你想让我再来一遍吗
I'm finished! Do you want me to say it again?
对 请再来一遍
Yes, please!
路西法喜欢坚持
Lucifer loves persistence.
就算她不是那个人 她也是使节
If she's not the one, she's the ambassador.
"我呼唤你来填满我的身体 我的灵魂..."
"I call on you to fill my body, my soul..."
关于这个乡巴佬音乐
Regarding this honky-tonk,
我传递信息遇到了困难
I'm having trouble delivering the message.
为什么
Why?
有两个相互矛盾的信息
There are two conflicting messages.
他们不相信你的
They don't believe yours.
他们不相信我 格蕾丝就活不了了
If they don't believe mine, Grace won't survive.
那请你给我一些能劝服他们的东西 求你了
Then give me something to convince them. Please.
我的妻子和我冒着生命危险在做这件事
My wife and I are putting our lives at risk doing this.
我理解 帮帮我
I understand. Help me.
去找刘 别找席
Talk to Lau, not Xi.
"去找刘 别找席"
"Talk to Lau, not Xi"?
爪子友好宠物医院
Paws & Claws Friendly Vet Services.
请在哔声后留言
Please leave a message after the beep.
"去找刘谈 别找席"
"Talk to Lau, not Xi."
来电 一个朋友
你好
Hello?
你从哪里知道的
Where did you get that?
从我们之前讨论过的情报源那里
From the source I discussed earlier.
他说如果你不相信他 格蕾丝就要死了
He said if you don't believe him, Grace won't survive.
你暴露了我们
You compromised us.
不 我什么都没做 除了传递信息
No, I haven't done anything but deliver a message.
现在该你做决定了
Now it's up to you.
先生
Sir?
2200列克星敦 楼下
2200 Lexington. Downstairs.
礼拜堂
The Chapel.
你想让我过去
You want me to come?
维克多·勒孔特
Victor LeConte?
维克多·勒孔特让我来这
Victor LeConte mi ha chiesto di venire qui.
我来接待他
Mi occuperoò io di lui.
我不明白还能有什么让你疑虑 席部长
罗马教廷信守其诺言
这将被视为教牧问题
而非政治问题
别人怎么告诉你 你就怎样复述给他
You need to tell him exactly as it was told to you.
你只有几秒钟时间
You'll only have a few seconds.
我代表梵蒂冈国务卿
无条件接受
洪伟主教和姚舜主教
以换取贵国政府释放和交换
编号242357的再教育人员
在这等着
Wait here.
对不起 先生
Mi scusi, Signor.
我们的中间人有您必须知道的信息
Our intermediary has heard information that you must know.
你有什么信息
What did you hear?
去找刘谈 别找席
Parla a Lau, non a Xi.
给你传递这条信息的男人
你相信他吗
是的 非常相信
Yes. Very much.
谢谢
Thank you.
席部长 我不会再和你说话了
我应该和刘先生说话
您才有权与我达成此协议
你做得非常好
You did very well.
梵蒂冈会很高兴的 现在回家吧
The Vatican will be pleased. Now go home.
格蕾丝会怎么样 她在哪
What about Grace? Where is she?
我们会解决的 回家吧
We'll find out. Go home.
哦
Oh!
我简直太棒了
I have made fire!
啊 啊
Ah, ah!
别让我失望
Don't disappoint me.
拜托
Come on.
嘣
Boop.
那个巫师球 玩偶匣
All right, so, the Wizard Ball, the jack-in-the-box,
公主魔杖 都是在
the Princess Wand, they were all manufactured
中国的同一个省制造的
in the same province in China.
- 真的假的 - 嗯
- Really? - Yeah.
本认为他们都是在同一个劳工营生产的
Ben thinks they were all produced at the same labor camps.
对 而这些
Yeah, and these
是劳工们发出的信息
were messages that were being sent out by the workers.
不是那个手指 那个是机器故障导致的
Not the finger. That was just malfunctioning machinery.
我认为他们是个地下组织的一部分
I think they're part of an underground organization
为的是将秘密信息从中国劳工营传递出去
used to transfer secret messages out of Chinese labor camps.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
维克多·勒孔特
Victor LeConte.
维克多·勒孔特和这件事
What does Victor LeConte
有什么关系
have to do with any of this?
独立体正试图将格蕾丝·林从中国救出来
The Entity is trying to get Grace Ling out of China.
- 我的天 真的吗 - 嗯
- Oh, my God. Seriously? - Yes.
我们不应该把注意力引到玩具店
We shouldn't draw attention to the toy store.
这只会让他们受伤
We can only get them hurt.
理解
Understood.
不好意思 我得接个电话
Oh, sorry, I have to get this.
瓦莱丽
Valerie?
- 瓦莱丽 你还好吗 - 克里斯汀 我是罗根
- Valerie, are you okay? - Kristen, it's Logan.
瓦莱丽出事了
Something is happening to Valerie.
出什么事了 她需要救护车吗
What is it? Uh, does she need an ambulance?
不 不 她不听我的
No, no. Uh, she won't listen to me.
她除了你 谁都不见
She refuses to see anyone but you.
她羊水破了吗
Okay, um, has her water broke?
- 我不知道 - 好 我马上来
- I... I don't know. - All right, I'll be right there.
克里斯汀
Kristen.
- 我得走了 - 我得先说点什么
- I have to head out. - I need to say something first.
我不想让你
I don't want to disappoint you,
或者我自己失望
or myself.
但是我确信一些超越我们两人的东西
But I do believe in something that goes beyond both of us.
我知道你不相信上帝 但是我信
I know you don't believe in God, but I do.
而那需要我采取越过我们关系的行为
And that requires an action that is beyond what we have.
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know how else to say it,
但是我比我认识的任何人都更关心你
but I care for you more than anyone I know.
可是当上帝对我有所求时
But when God demands something of me...
我必须服从
... I have to obey.
我也希望我能理解
I wish I understood.
我明白 没有关系
I know. That's okay.
只要你知道你对我有多重要
As long as you know how much you matter to me.
大卫 我爱你
David, I love you.
我不想说这些 因为听起来像是
I hate saying that, because it sounds like
我言不由衷
I mean something that I don't.
但是我的确爱你 我爱你如朋友
But I love you. I love you as a friend,
我爱你如我尊敬的人
I love you as somebody I respect.
如...
Somebody who...
我最好别说了
Look, I should probably just stop talking.
我该走了
I should go.
好
Good.
罗根
Logan?
瓦莱丽
Valerie?
瓦莱丽 有人吗
Valerie? Hello?
罗根
Logan.
瓦莱丽在哪里
Where's Valerie?
我想救她
I was trying to save her.
我得把它挖出来
I had to cut it out.
它会杀了她的
It was killing her.
天啊 你做了什么
Oh, my God. What did you do?
你做了什么
What did you do?!
谁在那
Hello?
大卫
David?
格蕾丝
Grace?
我听说是你救了我
I was told you were responsible for my release.
夸大其词了
That's overstating things.
并没有
It's not.
上帝知道你做了什么
God knows what you did.
上帝还知道你之后要做什么
And God knows what you'll do next.
谢谢
Thank you.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现